https://www.better-golf-by-putting-better.com/privacy-policy.html

Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better.com
Master Your Putting to Master Your Game
Menu
HomeEzinesFacebookPutting BlogPutting Reviews
Intro to PuttingUsing Web SitePutting InstructionPutting BasicsPutting Smarter
All about PuttersPutter FittingChoosing a Putter
Putting LessonsLesson Plan
Putting ImagesPutting Images
Setup at AddressFundamentals
Putting StraightPre-putt RoutinePutting StrokePractice Putting
Aiming Aiming Putterface
Tempo for DistanceDistance Control
Seeing the LineGreen ReadingGreen MappingGreen Mapping StepsPutt ReadingFall LineFall Line Putt Reader
Mental GameInside Your Head
Resources Putting VideosBooks on PuttingBook StorePutting Aids
MiscellaneousPutting RulesPutting CartoonsPutting QuotesGolf AnecdotesResourcesShort Game
SundryA to Z IndexAboutAbout This SiteContact FormDisclaimer
Home   |   About   |   About this Site   |   Contact   |   Site Search
Privacy Policy
Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better is committed to protecting your privacy and to giving you a secure online experience. We strive to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations.
The statement governs our Privacy Policy when you use the Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better site (the "Site"). Please read it. We hope it will help you to make an informed decision about sharing your personal information.You can page through most of this Site without revealing any information about yourself. There will be occasions when we will need information to provide any services that you request.This statement explains the types of personal information collected on those occasions as well as the steps taken to safeguard the information.By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy statement.Collecting Personal InformationWe collect personally identifiable information from visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.Generally this information is requested when you request information, participate in a poll or contest, or sign up to join an email list. Except for your name and email address, most of the time the information you provide is completely optional.Use of Personal InformationThe information collected is used to:Improve your overall experience on the Site.Deliver content that is most relevant to you.Notify you of any updates, if requested by you.Respond to any of your enquiries.Security of Personal InformationWhen you give us your personal information, we will only use it for the internal purposes stated above. It will NEVER be sold, bartered, or shared with any third parties without your permission.Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better uses a third party hosting provider to host the Site and the information you provide to us. The administration and maintenance of the servers on which our Site is hosted is performed by this third party.The personal information that you provide is kept securely on file with our hosting provider SiteSell Inc.Non-Personal InformationWhen you visit the Site, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically captured. This information includes:The name of your Internet service provider.The Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet.The date and time you access the Site.The pages that you access while at the Site.The Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our Site.None of this information is personally identifiable. This anonymous information is used to help improve the Site, analyse trends, and administer the Site. It is NOT shared with other organisations for commercial purposes.Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsWe may use cookies to help you to personalise your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser.The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of the site's services, a cookie enables us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.You have the ability to accept or decline the cookies by modifying your Web browser. However, if you choose to decline the cookies, you will still be able to view the text on the screen in the same way as if you had accepted the cookies.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single site or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on the Site to ascertain how many times you have seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on the Site.Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our Site, should you so choose.The search box on this Site (SiteSearch) is powered by Google Inc. (Google). You acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy(located at http://www.google.co.uk/privacy.html)shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to its privacy policy.Children's Online PrivacyThis Site is directed to adults - it is not directed to young children. We will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13 years, we will delete that information from our systems.Release of InformationIf Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better is sold, the information obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our Site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue.In that event, you will receive notice through our Site of that change in control and practices, and all reasonable efforts will be made to ensure that the purchaser honours any opt-out requests you might make.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this Privacy Policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our Site and would like that information deleted from the records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Form page.Changes to this StatementWe reserve the right to make changes to this statement. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, an indication will be made on our Site that they have changed with a link to the new Privacy Policy.You are encouraged to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information is collected and how it is used.Contact FormWe do not analyse, exchange, pass on, or otherwise make any use of the information you provide in the forms on this Site.Any information you provide in your email to us is treated in a strictly confidential manner and all necessary steps are taken to protect your privacy. We do not share any of this information with anyone.Outgoing LinksThis Site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site.We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. You should read the privacy statements of these linked sites before providing any personally identifiable information.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to our Privacy Policy as posted here in this document, please do not use this Site or any services offered by this Site.Your use of this Site indicates acceptance of this Privacy Policy.If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy statement or our use of your information, please contact us.
back to top
Return from Privacy Policy to Better Golf by Putting Better
HomeEzinesFacebookPutting BlogPutting ReviewsIntro to PuttingUsing Web SitePutting InstructionPutting BasicsPutting SmarterAll about PuttersPutter FittingChoosing a PutterPutting LessonsLesson PlanPutting ImagesPutting ImagesSetup at AddressFundamentalsPutting StraightPre-putt RoutinePutting StrokePractice PuttingAiming Aiming PutterfaceTempo for DistanceDistance ControlSeeing the LineGreen ReadingGreen MappingGreen Mapping StepsPutt ReadingFall LineFall Line Putt ReaderMental GameInside Your HeadResources Putting VideosBooks on PuttingBook StorePutting AidsMiscellaneousPutting RulesPutting CartoonsPutting QuotesGolf AnecdotesResourcesShort GameSundryA to Z IndexAboutAbout This SiteContact FormDisclaimer
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Use Your Languageto Read This Page
Use Your Language to Read This Page
Home   |   About   |   About this Site   |   Contact   |   Site Search
Original content copyright 2008-2020 Better-Golf-by-Putting-Better.com
All other content
is in the public domain or is copyright by credited author
